Subject Files
Marist Archives and Special Collections
- Subject Files, 2.1.3.6
  - Subject files: Softball (burros), undated; 8 (Box 1559)
    - [James H. "Jimmy" Doolittle, left], 8
    - L to R - Ed. Reek, mgr. edit. Fox MovieTone; Lew Lehr; Jack [?], Fox MovieTone cameraman, 9
    - Verso: L to R - Ed. Reek, mgr. edit. Fox MovieTone; Lew Lehr; Jack [?], Fox MovieTone cameraman, 9-verso
    - [L to R - Ed. Reek, mgr. edit. Fox MovieTone; Lew Lehr; Jack [?], Fox MovieTone cameraman], 10
    - [James H. "Jimmy" Doolittle, right], 11
    - [James H. "Jimmy" Doolittle, catching, Lew Lehr, at bat], 12
    - [Lew Lehr], 13
    - [Lew Lehr], 14
    - [Lowell Thomas, right], 15
    - [Man riding on a donkey], 16
    - [Man riding a donkey], 17
    - [Members of the softball team], 18
    - [Man standing next to a donkey], 19
  - Subject files: Softball (game photographs), circa 1930s; 9 (Box 1559)
    - John Roosevelt at bat, L.T. catching, 1
    - Verso: John Roosevelt at bat, L.T. catching, 1-verso
    - John Boettiger at bat, L.T. catching, 2
    - Verso: John Boettiger at bat, L.T. catching, 2-verso
    - Quentin Reynolds, L.T., Deems Taylor, 3
    - Verso: Quentin Reynolds, L.T., Deems Taylor, 3-verso
    - [Heywood] Broun, 4
    - Verso: [Heywood] Broun, 4-verso
    - [Heywood Broun], 5
    - Hollick-Kenyon, 6
    - Verso: Hollick-Kenyon, 6-verso
    - [Lowell Thomas, Jr.], 7
    - Col. Stoopnagle [F. Chase Taylor] gets a charley horse in the neck. Or maybe he's hunting for the ball, 8
    - Verso: Col. Stoopnagle [F. Chase Taylor] gets a charley horse in the neck. Or maybe he's hunting for the ball, 8-verso
    - [Prosper Buranelli], 9
    - Sir Hubert Wilkins, 10
    - Verso: Sir Hubert Wilkins, 10-verso
    - [Sir Hubert Wilkins], 11
    - [Sir Hubert Wilkins], 12
    - Dick Stoddart, famous radio engineer, who flew around the world with Howard Hughes. Stoddart get [sic] to 1st base. But he got a charley horse at this point and couldn't go farther. He could fly around the world but not around the bases; How Not to Dress, 13
    - Verso: Dick Stoddart, famous radio engineer, who flew around the world with Howard Hughes. Stoddart get [sic] to 1st base. But he got a charley horse at this point and couldn't go farther. He could fly around the world but not around the bases; How Not to Dress, 13-verso
    - Captain Frank Hawks getting ready to crash out a home run, 14
    - Verso: Captain Frank Hawks getting ready to crash out a home run, 14-verso
    - [Robert] Ripley on mound, 15
    - Note: [Robert] Ripley on mound, 16
    - L. Thomas [catching], 17
    - Verso: L. Thomas [catching], 17-verso
    - Dale "Slugger" Carnegie who occasionally played right field for The Nine Old Men. LT would put him in when he thought the opposing team, Pres. FDR "Roosevelt Packers," ought to be allowed a few runs!, 18
    - Note: Dale "Slugger" Carnegie who occasionally played right field for The Nine Old Men. LT would put him in when he thought the opposing team, Pres. FDR "Roosevelt Packers," ought to be allowed a few runs!, 19
    - Eddie Rickenbacker, 20
    - Verso: Eddie Rickenbacker, 20-verso
    - Frank Hawks, 21
    - Verso: Frank Hawks, 21-verso
    - Osa Johnson, Sir Hubert Wilkins, 22
    - Verso: Osa Johnson, Sir Hubert Wilkins, 22-verso
    - Frank Parker, 23
    - Verso: Frank Parker, 23-verso
    - Lanny Ross, 24
    - Verso: Lanny Ross, 24-verso
    - Grantland Rice and Heywood Broun, on their toes, as they share the responsibility of right field, 25
    - Note: Grantland Rice and Heywood Broun, on their toes, as they share the responsibility of right field, 26
    - [Men playing softball], 27
    - [Man hitting the softball], 28
    - Man running during a softball game], 29
    - [Man hitting the ball], 30
    - [Man getting ready to bat], 31
    - [Pitcher], 32
    - [Man standing in the outfield], 33
    - [Man getting ready to bat], 34
    - [Pitcher releasing the ball], 35
    - [Man cheering], 36
    - [Man sliding to base], 37
    - [Softball players], 38
    - [Cars in foreground, softball field in background], 39
  - Subject file: Softball (game photographs), circa 1930s; 10 (Box 1559)
    - Powell, 1
    - Verso: Powell, 1-verso
    - Capt. Frank Hawks, 2
    - Verso: Capt. Frank Hawks, 2-verso
    - Fifi D'Orsay, 3
    - Verso: Fifi D'Orsay, 3-verso
    - [Man up at bat], 4
    - [Pitcher standing on the mound], 5
    - [Man hitting the ball], 6
    - [Man hitting the ball], 7
    - [Man swining at the ball], 8
    - [Man hitting the ball], 9
    - [Softball player hitting the ball], 10
    - [Softball players in the field], 11
    - [Man up at bat], 12
    - [Man getting ready to swing], 13
  - Subject files: Softball (Meadowbrook game), 1937 October 17; 11 (Box 1559)
    - (Meadowbrook Game); Oct 17, 1937, 1
    - Verso: (Meadowbrook Game); Oct 17, 1937, 1-verso
    - L.T. team group pix [sic.] at Oyster Bay (Meadowbrook Game), 2
    - Verso: L.T. team group pix [sic.] at Oyster Bay (Meadowbrook Game), 2-verso
    - Meadowbrook Game, 3
    - Verso: Meadowbrook Game, 3-verso
    - [Sagamore Hill Oyster Bay, Meadowbrook Game], 4
    - Sagamore Hill Oyster Bay; Photograph by Roland Harvey, Nov 1937 "Pic", 5
    - Verso: Sagamore Hill Oyster Bay; Photograph by Roland Harvey, Nov 1937 "Pic", 5-verso
  - Subject files: Softball (Nine Old Men versus Ford Festival), undated; 12 (Box 1559)
    - Note: James Melton, opera singer, [Lowell Thomas, right], 1
    - [James Melton, L.T.], 2
    - [James Melton, L.T.], 3
    - James Melton, L.T., 4
    - Verso: James Melton, L.T., 4-verso
    - [James Melton, L.T.], 5
    - [Lowell Thomas], 6
    - [Lowell Thomas, right], 7
    - [Lowell Thomas at bat], 8
    - [Lowell Thomas at bat], 9
    - [Lowell Thomas, right], 10
  - Subject files: Softball (Nine Old Men versus Robert Ripley's Believe-It-Or-Nots), 1939; 13 (Box 1559)
    - [Robert Ripley], 1
    - [Robert Ripley], 2
    - [Robert Ripley], 3
    - [Lowell Thomas], 4
    - [Robert Ripley and Lowell Thomas], 5
    - [Robert Ripley and Lowell Thomas], 6
    - [Robert Ripley and Lowell Thomas], 7
    - LT and Bob Ripley at the Garden [Madison Square Garden] playing a benefit softball game; It would be appreciated if in publishing this picture you would give credit to "Paul Parker Photo", The Boys Club of New York, 8
    - Verso: LT and Bob Ripley at the Garden [Madison Square Garden] playing a benefit softball game; It would be appreciated if in publishing this picture you would give credit to "Paul Parker Photo", The Boys Club of New York, 8-verso
    - Lowell Thomas; Mayor Fiorello H. La Guardia; Robert L. Ripley; Photo by Charles Seawood, 9
    - Verso: Lowell Thomas; Mayor Fiorello H. La Guardia; Robert L. Ripley; Photo by Charles Seawood, 9-verso
    - Richards Vidmer and Heywood Broun; It would be appreciated if in publishing this picture you would give credit to "Paul Parker Photo", The Boys Club of New York, 10
    - Verso: Richards Vidmer and Heywood Broun; It would be appreciated if in publishing this picture you would give credit to "Paul Parker Photo", The Boys Club of New York, 10-verso
    - Napoleon [Les Kramer] and Graham McNamee at Atlantic City Fall of 1939, 11
    - Verso: Napoleon [Les Kramer] and Graham McNamee at Atlantic City Fall of 1939, 11-verso
    - [Napoleon (Les Kramer) and Lew Lehr], 12
    - Lew Lehr [right], Gene Tunney [left], Mad. [Madison] Square Garden It would be appreciated if in publishing this picture you would give credit to "Paul Parker Photo", The Boys Club of New York, 13
    - Verso: Lew Lehr [right], Gene Tunney [left], Mad. [Madison] Square Garden It would be appreciated if in publishing this picture you would give credit to "Paul Parker Photo", The Boys Club of New York, 13-verso
    - [Gene Tunney, second from left], 14
    - [Gene Tunney, third from left], 15
    - L to R: Col. Theodore Roosevelt, Jr. and Lowell Thomas; photo by Charles Seawood, 16
    - Verso: L to R: Col. Theodore Roosevelt, Jr. and Lowell Thomas; photo by Charles Seawood, 16-verso
    - Ted Husing; photo by Charles Seawood, 17
    - Verso: Ted Husing; photo by Charles Seawood, 17-verso
    - Showing Walter Johnson how to pitch at Mad. Sq. [Madison Square Garden], 18
    - Verso: Showing Walter Johnson how to pitch at Mad. Sq. [Madison Square Garden], 18-verso
    - [Showing Walter Johnson how to pitch at Mad. Sq. [Madison Square Garden]], 19
    - James Melton; Photo by Charles Seawood, 20
    - Verso: James Melton; Photo by Charles Seawood, 20-verso
    - [James Melton], 21
    - Catching- Tex O;Rourke, Congressman Hamilton Fish [at bat]; Photo by Charles Seawood, 22
    - Verso: Catching- Tex O;Rourke, Congressman Hamilton Fish [at bat]; Photo by Charles Seawood, 22-verso
    - LT and Sir Hubert Wilkins, 23
    - Verso: LT and Sir Hubert Wilkins, 23-verso
    - Please make a glossy about this size of this one., 24
    - Verso: Please make a glossy about this size of this one., 24-verso
    - [The "Nine Old Men" softball team. Lowell Thomas on top.], 25
    - [Softball player sitting in a chair], [3 copies], 26
    - [Softball players drinking], 27
    - [The "Nine Old Men" softball team], 28
  - Subject files: Softball (Nine Old Men versus the Statesmen in Washington, D.C.), 1941 June; 14 (Box 1559)
    - Cooling off the Vice-President; Washington, D.C. Senator James M. Mead of New York is pictured fanning Vice-President Wallace after the V-P crossed the plate with a run in the second inning of their annual game here in Washington. Lowell Thomas captained the "Nine Old Men" team, while Rep. Ham Fish of New York, led the "Statesman" team. The game played for charity, lasted eight innings and was won by the "Statesmen" by a score of 15-14; M-6-3-41..1240PM, 1
    - Note: Cooling off the Vice-President; Washington, D.C. Senator James M. Mead of New York is pictured fanning Vice-President Wallace after the V-P crossed the plate with a run in the second inning of their annual game here in Washington. Lowell Thomas captained the "Nine Old Men" team, while Rep. Ham Fish of New York, led the "Statesman" team. The game played for charity, lasted eight innings and was won by the "Statesmen" by a score of 15-14; M-6-3-41..1240PM, 2
    - Lowell Thomas's "Nine Old Men" Play the "Statesmen"; Washington- Left to right at the game today: Lowell Thomas; Walter Johnson; Sen. James M. Mead; and Vice-President Henry A. Wallace. At Griffith Stadium for the annual game of softball for charity. H-1-6/7/41 L, 3
    - Note: Lowell Thomas's "Nine Old Men" Play the "Statesmen"; Washington- Left to right at the game today: Lowell Thomas; Walter Johnson; Sen. James M. Mead; and Vice-President Henry A. Wallace. At Griffith Stadium for the annual game of softball for charity. H-1-6/7/41 L, 4
    - [L.T.'s Nine Old Men play the Statesmen], 5
    - Mrs. Henry Wallace throws the first ball to start a softball game in which a team led by her husband played a team known as the "Nine Old Men" and captained by Lowell Thomas. Lowell Thomas is to the right of Mrs. Wallace; 6-7-41, 6
    - Note: Mrs. Henry Wallace throws the first ball to start a softball game in which a team led by her husband played a team known as the "Nine Old Men" and captained by Lowell Thomas. Lowell Thomas is to the right of Mrs. Wallace; 6-7-41, 7
    - Batter up - Henry Wallace, 8
    - Note: Softball Ballgame in Washington Mrs. Henry Wallace; Batter up - Henry Wallace, 9
    - [Man swinging at the ball], 10
    - [Man watching the ball fly], 11
    - [Lowell Thomas and another ball player], 12
    - ["Nine Old Men" softball team], 13
    - [The Washington D.C. Team-The "Statesmen"], 14
  - Subject files: Softball (Nine Old Men and other team photographs), circa 1930s - early 1940s; 15 (Box 1559)
    - L.T. front row on right, and his famous soft ball team, 1
    - Note: L.T. front row on right, and his famous soft ball team, 2
    - Standing left to right - a group assembled for playing ball???.. Grantland Rice, next three question mark, Truman Talley 4 of 20th Century Fox, Gene Buck, head of ASCAP, Rube Goldberg, Merlin K. "Deac" Aylesworth, President of NBC, Homer Croy, novelist; Bill Carey DS on sweater, one of the builders of the Panama Canal; Paul Webb, cartoonist; Ted Shane, humorist; Doctor Frederick Gamage, headmaster and Robert Johnson President Temple Univ.; Seated - left - Arthur McGovern, referee; second unknown; Richard Vidmer, sports editor, Herald Trib.; General Theodore Roosevelt Jr.; John Kieran, New York Times; John Golden, producer; in front of Golden is Lew Lehr, humorist; L.T. in background; next question mark; in front Prosper Buranelli, author; Jack Pegler, advertising; Gil Hodges, publisher; Charles E. Murphy, justice?; Verso: Richard Vidmer, Arthur Donovan, Bill Carey, Gene Buck ASCAP, 3
    - Verso: Richard Vidmer, Arthur Donovan, Bill Carey, Gene Buck ASCAP, 3-verso
    - Note: Standing left to right - a group assembled for playing ball???.. Grantland Rice, next three question mark, Truman Talley 4 of 20th Century Fox, Gene Buck, head of ASCAP, Rube Goldberg, Merlin K. "Deac" Aylesworth, President of NBC, Homer Croy, novelist; Bill Carey DS on sweater, one of the builders of the Panama Canal; Paul Webb, cartoonist; Ted Shane, humorist; Doctor Frederick Gamage, headmaster and Robert Johnson President Temple Univ.; Seated - left - Arthur McGovern, referee; second unknown; Richard Vidmer, sports editor, Herald Trib.; General Theodore Roosevelt Jr.; John Kieran, New York Times; John Golden, producer; in front of Golden is Lew Lehr, humorist; L.T. in background; next question mark; in front Prosper Buranelli, author; Jack Pegler, advertising; Gil Hodges, publisher; Charles E. Murphy, justice?, 4
    - [Standing left to right - a group assembled for playing ball???.. Grantland Rice, next three question mark, Truman Talley 4 of 20th Century Fox, Gene Buck, head of ASCAP, Rube Goldberg, Merlin K. "Deac" Aylesworth, President of NBC, Homer Croy, novelist; Bill Carey DS on sweater, one of the builders of the Panama Canal; Paul Webb, cartoonist; Ted Shane, humorist; Doctor Frederick Gamage, headmaster and Robert Johnson President Temple Univ.; Seated - left - Arthur McGovern, referee; second unknown; Richard Vidmer, sports editor, Herald Trib.; General Theodore Roosevelt Jr.; John Kieran, New York Times; John Golden, producer; in front of Golden is Lew Lehr, humorist; L.T. in background; next question mark; in front Prosper Buranelli, author; Jack Pegler, advertising; Gil Hodges, publisher; Charles E. Murphy, justice?; Verso: Richard Vidmer, Arthur Donovan, Bill Carey, Gene Buck ASCAP], 5
    - Verso: Richard Vidmer, Arthur Donovan, Bill Carey, Gene Buck, 5-verso
    - [Standing left to right - a group assembled for playing ball???.. Grantland Rice, next three question mark, Truman Talley 4 of 20th Century Fox, Gene Buck, head of ASCAP, Rube Goldberg, Merlin K. "Deac" Aylesworth, President of NBC, Homer Croy, novelist; Bill Carey DS on sweater, one of the builders of the Panama Canal; Paul Webb, cartoonist; Ted Shane, humorist; Doctor Frederick Gamage, headmaster and Robert Johnson President Temple Univ.; Seated - left - Arthur McGovern, referee; second unknown; Richard Vidmer, sports editor, Herald Trib.; General Theodore Roosevelt Jr.; John Kieran, New York Times; John Golden, producer; in front of Golden is Lew Lehr, humorist; L.T. in background; next question mark; in front Prosper Buranelli, author; Jack Pegler, advertising; Gil Hodges, publisher; Charles E. Murphy, justice?; Verso: Richard Vidmer, Arthur Donovan, Bill Carey, Gene Buck ASCAP], 6
    - Verso: [mostly illegible], 6-verso
    - L.T. and the Debtors & Creditors; L.T. sitting in the middle, 7
    - Verso: L.T. and the Debtors & Creditors; L.T. sitting in the middle, 7-verso
    - LT sitting in the middle and his softball team, 8
    - Verso: LT sitting in the middle and his softball team, 8-verso
    - [Nine Old Men lineup for game against Saugatuck Saviors; Standing: John McCarten, Paul Webb, F. Chase Taylor (Col. Stoopnagle), Robert Lansden, Tex O'Rourke Seated: Wood Cowan, L.T., Captain Frank Hawks and Ted Shane], 9
    - Nine Old Men lineup for game against Saugatuck Saviors; Standing: John McCarten, Paul Webb, F. Chase Taylor (Col. Stoopnagle), Robert Lansden, Tex O'Rourke Seated: Wood Cowan, L.T., Captain Frank Hawks and Ted Shane, 10
    - Verso: Nine Old Men lineup for game against Saugatuck Saviors; Standing: John McCarten, Paul Webb, F. Chase Taylor (Col. Stoopnagle), Robert Lansden, Tex O'Rourke Seated: Wood Cowan, L.T., Captain Frank Hawks and Ted Shane, 10-verso
    - Col. Stoopnagle [F. Chase Taylor], 11
    - Verso: Col. Stoopnagle [F. Chase Taylor], 11-verso
    - [Washington D.C. (?) softball team], 12
    - [Washington D.C. (?) softball team], 13
    - [Lowell Thomas standing with a softball team], 14
    - [Lowell Thomas with a softball team], 15
    - [Softball team], 16
    - [Softball team], 17
    - [Softball team], 18
    - [Softball team], 19
    - [Softball team], 20
    - [Softball team], 21
    - [Softball team], 22
    - [Women's softball team], 23
    - [Softball team], 24
    - [Softball team], 25
    - [Softball team], 26
    - [Softball team], 27
    - [Softball team], 28
    - [Softball team], 29
    - [Softball team], 30
    - [Softball team], 31
    - [Softball teams], 32
    - [Softball team], 33
    - [Softball team], 34
    - [Softball team], 35
  - Subject files: Softball (Nine Old Men and other team photographs), circa 1930s - early 1940s; 16 (Box 1559)
    - [Nine Old Men softball team], 1
    - [Nine Old Men softball team], 2
    - [Softball teams], 3
    - [Softball team], 4
    - [Softball team], 5
    - [Softball team], 6
    - [Lowell Thomas standing with members of a softball team], 7
  - Subject files: Softball (Nine Old Men), circa 1955; 17 (Box 1559)
    - This is the one we should have done up at least it seems to be the better of the two of the group; [standing, left to right]: LT Jr., Ted Shane, George Hicks, Bill Spence, Gene Tunney, Count Luckner, Cal Durgin, Paul Webb; [kneeling, left to right]: Peter Grimm, Eddie Eagan, LT, Gene Sarazen, Lanny Ross, 1
    - Note: This is the one we should have done up at least it seems to be the better of the two of the group; [standing, left to right]: LT Jr., Ted Shane, George Hicks, Bill Spence, Gene Tunney, Count Luckner, Cal Durgin, Paul Webb; [kneeling, left to right]: Peter Grimm, Eddie Eagan, LT, Gene Sarazen, Lanny Ross, 2
  - Subject files: Softball (other team photographs), circa 1930s - 1941; 18 (Box 1559)
    - [Kodak Park softball team] Infeilders, left to right: Krembel, 2nd base; Castle, 1st base; Bender, short fielder; Sparks, 3rd base; Gallagher, shortstop, 1
    - Verso: [Kodak Park softball team] Infeilders, left to right: Krembel, 2nd base; Castle, 1st base; Bender, short fielder; Sparks, 3rd base; Gallagher, shortstop, 1-verso
    - [Kodak Park softball team] Outfielders: Galisano; Flynn; Reisinger; Norton; Werth; Stevens, 2
    - Verso: [Kodak Park softball team] Outfielders: Galisano; Flynn; Reisinger; Norton; Werth; Stevens, 2-verso
    - Kodak Park Softball Team, 1941, 3
    - Verso: Kodak Park Softball Team, 1941, 3-verso
    - [Kodak Park Softball Team, 1941], 4
    - [Kodak Park pitcher], 5
    - [Kodak Park pitcher], 6
    - To Lowell Thomas from Mike Shipley and 6th Ward Citizens Association Softball Club, Lancaster, Pa. [Pennsylvania], 7
    - Verso: To Lowell Thomas from Mike Shipley and 6th Ward Citizens Association Softball Club, Lancaster, Pa. [Pennsylvania], 7-verso
  Box 1560
- Subject Files, 2.1.3.6
  - Subject files: Softball (Quaker Hill) [contact sheets], circa 1930s - early 1940s; 1 (Box 1560)
    - [contact sheets of Softball at Quaker Hill], 1
    - [contact sheets of Softball at Quaker Hill], 2
    - [contact sheets of Softball at Quaker Hill], 3
    - [contact sheets of Softball at Quaker Hill], 4
    - [contact sheets of Softball at Quaker Hill], 5
    - [contact sheets of Softball at Quaker Hill], 6
    - [contact sheets of Softball at Quaker Hill], 7
  - Subject files: Softball (President Franklin Delano Roosevelt), circa 1930s; 2 (Box 1560)
    - [Lowell Thomas with President Franklin Delano Roosevelt], 1
    - [Lowell Thomas next to President Franklin Deano Roosevelt], 2
    - [Lowell Thomas speaking with President Franklin Delano Roosevelt], 3
    - [Franklin Delano Roosevely talking to a man], 4
    - [Franklin Delano Roosevelt speaking with Lowell Thomas], 5
    - [Franklin Delano Roosevelt and Lowell Thomas], 6
    - [Lowell Thomas, watching a band while President Franklin Delano Roosevelt talks to two people from his car], 7
    - [President Franklin Delano Roosevelt talking with a man], 8
    - [Lowell Thomas, watching a band while President Franklin Delano Roosevelt talks to two people from his car], 9
    - [Lowell Thomas talking with President Franklin Delano Roosevelt], 10
    - [President Franklin Delano Roosevelt], 11
    - [President Franklin Delano Roosevelt talking to a man], 12
  - Subject files: Softball (Babe Ruth), 1937; 3 (Box 1560)
    - [Babe Ruth], 1
    - Walsh; Photograph by Roland Harvey, Nov 1937 "Pic", 2
    - Verso: Walsh; Photograph by Roland Harvey, Nov 1937 "Pic", 2-verso
    - [Babe Ruth], 3
  - Subject files: Softball (Colonel Lemuel Q. Stoopnagle [F. Chase Taylor]), circa 1930s; 4 (Box 1560)
    - Lowell Thomas signing up Colonel Stoopnagle to play on his softball team, the Nine Old Men, 1
    - Verso: Lowell Thomas signing up Colonel Stoopnagle to play on his softball team, the Nine Old Men, 1-verso
    - Lowell Thomas signing up Colonel Stoopnagle to play on his softball team, the Nine Old Men, 2
    - Verso: Lowell Thomas signing up Colonel Stoopnagle to play on his softball team, the Nine Old Men, 2-verso
    - [Lowell Thomas signing up Colonel Stoopnagle to play on his softball team, the Nine Old Men], 3
    - [Lowell Thomas signing up Colonel Stoopnagle to play on his softball team, the Nine Old Men], 4
    - [Lowell Thomas signing up Colonel Stoopnagle to play on his softball team, the Nine Old Men], 5
    - [Lowell Thomas signing up Colonel Stoopnagle to play on his softball team, the Nine Old Men], 6
    - [Lowell Thomas signing up Colonel Stoopnagle to play on his softball team, the Nine Old Men], 7
    - [Colonel Stoopnagle signing up with Lowell Thomas to play on his softball team, the Nine Old Men], 8
    - [Colonel Stoopnagle signing up with Lowell Thomas to play on his softball team, the Nine Old Men], 9
    - [Colonel Stoopnagle signing up with Lowell Thomas to play on his softball team, the Nine Old Men], 10
    - [Colonel Stoopnagle signing up with Lowell Thomas to play on his softball team, the Nine Old Men], 11
    - [Colonel Stoopnagle signing up with Lowell Thomas to play on his softball team, the Nine Old Men], 12
    - [Colonel Stoopnagle signing up with Lowell Thomas to play on his softball team, the Nine Old Men], 13
    - [Colonel Stoopnagle signing up with Lowell Thomas to play on his softball team, the Nine Old Men], 14
    - [Colonel Stoopnagle signing up with Lowell Thomas to play on his softball team, the Nine Old Men], 15
    - [Colonel Stoopnagle signing up to play softball on Lowell Thomas's team, the Nine Old Men], 16
    - [Colonel Stoopnagle signing up to play softball on Lowell Thomas's team, the Nine Old Men], 17
    - [Colonel Stoopnagle signing up to play softball on Lowell Thomas's team, the Nine Old Men], 18
    - [Colonel Stoopnagle signing up to play softball on Lowell Thomas's team, the Nine Old Men], 19
    - [Colonel Stoopnagle signing up to play softball on Lowell Thomas's team, the Nine Old Men], 20
  - Subject files: Softball (Lowell Thomas, Jr.), 1930s; 5 (Box 1560)
    - [Lowell Thomas, Jr. with Jim Thorpe], 1
    - [Lowell Thomas, Jr. with Jim Thorpe], 2
    - [Lowell Thomas and his softball team], 3
    - [A group of men dressed as women], 4